JUSTIN NGOV

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

☑ jngov@asu.edu **८** (602) 410 9602 **in** justinngov

SUMMARY

Passionate and driven individual who excels in learning and adapting to different situations. Computer Science background having accomplished projects along with work in the customer service field with 3+ years of experience resolving product and service issues. Eager to grow more as a person and contribute to team success.

EDUCATION

Arizona State University

Aug. 2019 - May 2023

BS Computer Science 2023 Barrett, The Honors College GPA: 4.0/4.0

PROJECTS

Aisha Comfortable Coliving Web Application

Jan. 2022 - Dec. 2022

- Worked on developing the Aisha Comfortable Coliving web application along with their mobile application.
- HTML, CSS, and JavaScript was used to construct the front-end of the web application.
- Experience using React Native as the framework of the mobile application.
- Utilized Postgres and PHP in the back-end database.
- Implemented profile specific views depending on what type of user account was signed in.

Honors Thesis: Artificially Intelligent Chatbots

Jan. 2022 - Dec. 2022

- Took on a personal project of developing an artificial chatbot for Aisha Comfortable Coliving.
- · Researched and implemented methods such as creating my own feedforward neural network, utilizing OpenAl GPT3, and IBM Watson.
- Utilized and PyTorch principles in order to understand machine learning.
- Fine tuned the language/personality of the chatbot in order to optimize performance and user satisfaction through the use of participant surveys.
- Experience using cloud solutions such as IBM Watson and Google Dialogflow.

PinIt (IOS Application) May 2022

- Swift based application that allowed the user to capture images and associate them with the location they were taken at along with tagging a song.
- Utilized iTunes Search API to allow users to search for songs using autocompletion suggestions.
- Implemented geocoding functionality to track users locations.
- · Application was built keeping the MVC architecture in mind, and personal creativity was used for the UI design.
- $\bullet \ \ \mathsf{Applied} \ \mathsf{UlImagePickerView} \ \mathsf{for} \ \mathsf{both} \ \mathsf{IOS} \ \mathsf{Camera} \ \mathsf{and} \ \mathsf{Photo} \ \mathsf{Library} \ \mathsf{accesss}.$

EMPLOYMENT

Education at Work, Microsoft Surface Support Specialist, Tempe, Arizona

Feb. 2020 - Current

- Assisted North American businesses' infrastructure by providing support to their Surface devices.
- Aided Microsoft in spearheading the addition the first North American based Surface support center by taking on the first commercial customers and teaching my peers that came later.
- Experienced in using IT support ticketing systems to manage multiple support cases at a time.
- · Consistently received top marks from commercial customers regarding level of satisfaction and overall professionalism.
- Skills acquired during this position include: Microsoft Azure Active Directory, Windows Troubleshooting Knowledge, Office 365 Proficiency, Leadership Skills, and Resourcefulness

Desert Forest Golf Club, Caddie, Carefree, Arizona

Nov. 2017 - Jan. 2019

- Applied years of experience playing and watching golf to assist club members during their rounds via strategic advice or more technical swing/putting advice.
- Worked efficiently with club members and other caddies keeping up the pace of play.
- Built rapport with many members and became their regulars.

SKILLS